▍2026 美网 女单四分之一决赛
萨巴伦卡 7-6¹ 3-6 7-6⁷ 诺斯科娃 · 赛后场上采访
Aryna, incredible match.
阿丽娜 这场球太不可思议了
That was some incredible tennis.
刚才的网球实在太精彩了
First set, you played really well.
第一盘你打得非常好
Second set, Linda raised her level.
第二盘琳达提升了状态
You were down a break in the third,
第三盘你一度落后一个破发
and then you went to another gear.
随后你又提升了一个档次
What made the difference in that third set?
第三盘是什么带来了变化
Yeah, oh my God, guys.
是啊 天哪 各位
what a battle,
真是一场苦战
what an incredible player she is.
她真是个不可思议的选手
And I'm speechless right now,
我现在激动得说不出话来
because I was pushing myself to the limit
因为我一直把自己逼到极限
in this match, especially in the third set.
这场比赛 尤其是第三盘
I I honestly thought that that's it.
我当时真的以为就这样了
The match is over.
比赛结束了
And probably that's what helped me
可能正是这个念头帮助了我
to kind of like I don't know feel loose
让我 怎么说呢 放松了下来
and just go after my shots.
然后放开手脚去击球
And yeah, super happy to get this win.
真的特别开心能赢下这场球
Super happy. Yeah, it's tough match,
特别开心 这真是一场硬仗
tough battle.
一场苦战
Thank you guys for for honestly,
真心感谢大家
just for you guys being you.
谢谢你们一直做你们自己
You're amazing,
你们太棒了
and it's it's always unbelievable playing
每次打球都让我感觉不可思议
in front of you all.
尤其是在你们面前
Thank you for your support.
谢谢你们的支持
Match point, second serve.
赛点 面对二发
You go really aggressive and hit an ace.
你大胆出手 发出了一记 ACE
You haven't lost a tiebreaker here
你在这里的抢七还没输过
in 10 attempts at the US Open.
美网十次抢七全部获胜
Do you get more confidence
你会因此更有信心吗
on critical moments on this court?
在这片球场的关键时刻
Well, this kind of matches,
这样的比赛
this kind of tie- tie breaks, and this matches
这样的抢七 这样的较量
under such high pressure, definitely kind
在如此高压之下 确实
of like boosting my confidence
让我更有信心
and my energy and my motivation.
也让我更有能量和动力
So, I'm super glad that somehow I made
所以我特别高兴能发出
that ace, It was very important point.
那记 ACE 那一分非常重要
And it just shows that I'm ready to fight,
这说明我已经准备好战斗
and I'm happy to see that.
我很高兴看到这一点
Back into the semifinals.
你又回到了半决赛
Back into the semifinals here in New York.
又回到了纽约的半决赛
What are you gonna look to work
接下来你打算练些什么
on in the off days to improve to get ready?
利用休息日提升状态备战
Maybe a bit better game on the net,
也许把网前技术练得更好些
to be honest.
说实话
I think today couple times I approached
我觉得今天有几次我来到
the net but I wasn't quite ready.
网前 但并没有完全准备好
So, I think we'll work a little bit extra
所以我们会额外多练一点
on that part of my game.
我在这方面的技术
But you know what, we better ask my team.
不过 最好还是问问我的团队
Maybe they have a better plan for me,
也许他们有更好的安排
but for now, I just want to you know,
但现在我只想
relax, recover, and yeah just reflect
放松 恢复 再好好回想一下
on what just happened.
刚刚发生的这一切
Well done.
打得漂亮
Go get some rest.
去好好休息吧
Back into the semifinals again,
再次闯入半决赛
world number one Aryna Sabalenka.
世界第一 阿丽娜萨巴伦卡